U.S. Task Force on Rail Transportation. St. Louis Terminal Project Files 5714
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Task Force on Rail Transportation. St. Louis Terminal Project Files
1970-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Task Force on Rail Transportation
5714
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Annual reports, completion reports, experiment information, meeting information, progress reports and task for correspondence
3123186
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 19, 2003
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroad terminals -- United States.; Labor-management committees -- United States -- Sources.; Task Force on Rail Transportation (U.S.)
3123186
- Alton Lock and Dam No.26 & Second Lock (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2-6)
- Buffalo Terminal Project (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Car Utilization Program (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chicago Project (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
- Completion Report, No. 1 - Lesperance-Ivory Terminal Transfer (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Completion Report, No.3 - An Analysis of Cars Delivered in Interchange (Car Hire, Hourly per Diem vs. Daily) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Completion Report No.5 - Trans-River Transfer (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Completion Report No.7 - Remote Control Switch - Kirkwood (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Completion Report - Experiment No.9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Completion Report - No.10 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Completion Report No. 12 - Changes in Car Distribution (Car Service Rules) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Completion Report No. 13 - Yard Crews Assisting Road Trains Outside Switching Limits (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Completion Report No.15 - Valley Junction Experiment (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Completion Report No. l6 - Lesperance -23rd Street Transfer (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Completion Report No.18 - 23rd St.-Ivory (Heavy-Hauler) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Completion Report No.20 - Trans-River Transfer Scheduling (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Completion Report No.21 - Ivory Crews Assisting Road Trains Within Switching Limits (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Completion Report No.22 - Rover Switch Engine Assignment (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Completion Report No.23 - Local Freight Train Operation -SMLO to KC (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Completion Report No.24 - Car Conditioning (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Completion Report - Task I (SLT-l) Dupo-Madison Interchange Transfer (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Completion Report (1981) SLT-l - Terminal Information Exchange System (Prog.) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Completion Report (1981) SLT-2 - Establishing Common Labor Pools (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Completion Report - SLT-2 - Expediting Traffic by-Changing Car Hire Responsibility (A&S-SSW), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Scope and Contents
  3/10/1981
- Completion Report - Task I (SLT-3) - Reduce ATSF Rejects on MRS (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Completion Report - Task I (SLT-4) - Interchange between MRS & MOPAC (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Completion Report - (SLT-5) - Expedite St. Louis - Arlington, TX GMC Auto Traffic (TRRA-MOPAC) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Completion Report - Task I (SLT-6) - Reduce SSW Car Rejects on MRS Railway (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Completion Report - Task I (SLT-7) - St. Louis-Kansas City MOPAC-ATSF Run Thru (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Completion Report - SLT -8 - L&N Run-Thru to MOPAC (West), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  3/27/1981
- Completion Report - SLT-9 - Barriers to the Expanded Use of Trackage Right in the St. Louis Gateway (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Completion Report - SLT-10 - Establish TRRA Industry Car Distribution (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Completion Report - Task III - 3 (SLT-ll) - Train Guide (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Completion Report - SLT-12 - Rerouting MP-ICG Lime Traffic (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Completion Report - SLT-13 - St. Louis Terminal Information Exchange System (Ties): Phase I - Application and Scope, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  4/10/1981
- Completion Report - Task 2 - Terminal Performance Measurement System (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Completion Report - Task 3 - Coordination Between Railroads (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Completion Report - Task 4 - Employee/Management Communications (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Completion Report - Task IV-1 - Data Quality Analysis (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Completion Report - Task IV-2 - Analytical Capabilities of TPMS (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Completion Report SL-1 - Task 6 - A.O. Smith Auto Frame Traffic (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Completion Report - Task 7 - Expediting Traffic Between SOU&MOPAC (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Completion Report - SL-2-Task 9.1 - Expediting Fair Fax Industry Traffic (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Completion Report - Task 9.2 - Expedite Traffic Between MP/SLSF/Carrie Ave.-TRRA (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Completion Report - Task 9.3 - Expedite Empty Cars Between MP/CR-CNW-ICG (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Completion Report - Task 9.4 - Expedite Empty Cars Between MP/CS-MKT-SLSF (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Completion Report - Task 9.5 - Expedite Empty Cars Between MP/ATSF-RI-GTW (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Completion Report - Task 9.6 - Expedite Empty Cars Between MP/BN-IT-UP (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Completion Report - Task 9.7 - Expedite Empty Cars Between MP/L&N-MILW (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Completion Report - Task 9.8 - Expedite Empty Cars Between ICG&SOU (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Completion Report - Task 9.9 - Seminar on Interchange of Empty Cars (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Completion Report - Task 9.10 - Expedite Movement of Private Ownership Cars (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Completion Report - Task 9.11 - Analysis Programs (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Completion Report - Task 9.12 - Data Exchange on Empty Cars Between ICG/CR/BN/MD (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Completion Report - Task 10 - Users Guide (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Conference on Comm. Impact of Unit Coal Trains St. Louis, Mo., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  July 25-2T, 19T9
- Correspondence - V.G. Dyer, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Discipline Standards (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Employee and Railfan Assistance for Special Agents (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Employee Assistance Program (Alcohol Abuse) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Employee Awareness Program (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Empty Car Steering Committee (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Engineering Foundation Conference - Santa Barbara, Cal. (Miramar), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Sept. 1975
- Evaluation of Changes in Terminal Operations (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Expansion of St. Louis Project (MOPAC) to St. Louis Gateway (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Experiment Sites (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Experiment Status (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Experiments (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Experiments No. 1 - No. 4 (Box 4, Folder 2-6)
- Experiment No. 4-A - Training Supplement to Safety (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Experiments No. 5-9 (Box 4, Folder 8-12)
- Experiment No. 10 - Outside Hostlers (T-l) (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Experiment No. 11 - Dupo to Madison Transfers (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Experiment No. 12 - Clearing House on Car Service Rules (T-10) (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Experiment No. 12 - Copies of Clearing House Experiment Evaluation Approach (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Experiment No. 13 - Yard Crews Assisting Road Trains (T-3) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Experiment No. I4 - Motor Carts for Carmen (T-4) (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Experiment No. 15 - Trans-River Transfer Interchange at Va-ley Junction Yard (T-5) (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Experiment No. 16 - Transfer between 12th St. and Lesperance (T-7) (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Experiment No. I7 - Labadie Coal Trains (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Experiment No. 18 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Experiment No. l8S - Analysis of Terminal Operations (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Experiment No. 19, 19S (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
- Experiment No. 20 Improvements in Trans-River Transfer Scheduling (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Experiment No. 21 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Experiment No. 22 - Rover Switch Engine Assignment (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Experiment No. 23 - Local Freight Train Operation - St. Louis to Kansas City (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Experiment No. 24 - Car Conditioning (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Experiment No. 25 - St. Louis - Kansas City AT&SF Run-Through Train (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Experiment No. 26 - Expediting Piggy Back Movements (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Experiment SL-1 - Task 6 - A.O. Smith Auto Frame Traffic (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Experiment SL-2 - Task 9.1 - Expedite Fair fax Traffic (K.C.) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Experiment SL-4 - Task 7 - Expediting MOPAC-SOU Traffic (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Experiment SL-5 - Tasks 9.3-9-7 - Expediting Empty Cars (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Experiment MP Trackage Rights Over TRRA - Gratiof to Grand Avenue (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Experiment SL-6 - Task 9.2 - MP&SLSF Blocking TRRA-Carrie Ave. Traffic (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Experiment SL-12 - Empty Private Car Experiment (Box 5, Folder 7)
- FRA Regulations - Proposed Experiment (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Gateway Performance Statistics (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Grain Study (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Houston Experimentation - 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Houston Experimentation - 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- II-2 - Improving Radio Communication, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Intermodal Contract & Budget - General (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Intermodal - MOPAC Experiments (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Intermodal - Network Study (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Intermodal Operations - ICG Railroad (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Intermodal Project Team (Box 5, Folder 18)
- K.C. Experiment #2 - Interchange xfer Assignment Agreement (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Kansas City Project (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Kansas City Terminal Experimentation (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Labor Agreements (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Labor Management Committee (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Meetings and Correspondence - General and Local Chairmen (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Meetings - St. Louis Project (Expanded) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Meetings and Presentations - General (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Milwaukee Railroad Project (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Milwaukee, UTU & FRA Workshop, Itasca, Illinois, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Nov. 15-19,1976
- Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Monthly Report to Task Force Members (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Railway Utilization Corp. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- New England Project (Box 6, Folder 9)
- New Orleans Terminal Project (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Operating Procedure No. 1, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  1-May-75
- Portland Project (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Presentations (Misc.) (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Progress Reports AAR-FRR (monthly)- (contract), 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 14-19)
- Progress Reports (monthly) AAR-FRA, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  April 1979 - Jan. I98O Contract
- Progress Reports - AAR (Quarterly) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Progress Reports (Monthly), 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Public Relations, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
- II-3 Quality Circles, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- REAP (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Railroad Reliability and Freight Car Utilization Workshop -MIT, Cambridge, Mass., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Railroad Research Information Service (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 1 Reading File, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11-16)
  U/16/75-12/31/80
- Regional Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Reimbursement of Lost Earnings, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- Reorganization of the Task Force on Terminals to Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Restructuring the Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Road Haul Experimentation (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Seminar on "Ecology of Work II" St. Louis, Mo., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  June 18-20, 1980
- Seminar on Interchange Empty Cars, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Seminar on Measurement of Terminal Performance, Chicago, 111., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  May 21-22, 1975
- Seminar on TPMS, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  21-May-80
- Shippers Advisory Board (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Shipper Meetings (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Survey-Terminal Employees (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Survey of Traffic - St. Louis Terminal (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Task Force Correspondence - General, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Task Force Correspondence - General, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Task Force Correspondence - General, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Task Force Meetings, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 2-21)
  1973-1977 (April)
- Task Force Meetings, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 1-16)
  July 1977 - Dec. 1980